Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Recordings, Rock, Roll and Remember (RRR)
  - Show #91-13/477, March 30-31, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 358)
  - Show #91-14/478, April 6-7, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 358)
  - Show #91-15/479, April 13-14, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 358-359)
    Year/source: 1962 (LP)
  - Show #91-16/480, April 20-21, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 359)
  - Show #91-17/481, April 27-28, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 359)
  - Show #91-18/482, May 4-5, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 359-360)
  - Show #91-19/483, May 11-12, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 360)
  - Show #91-20/484, May 18-19, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 360-361)
  - Show #91-21/485, May 25-26, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 361)
  - Show #91-22/486, June 1-2, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 361)
  - Show #91-23/487, June 8-9, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 362)
  - Show #91-24/488, June 15-16, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 362)
  - Show #91-25/489, June 22-23, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 362-363)
  - Show #91-26/490, June 29-30, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 363)
  - Show #91-27/491, July 6-7, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 363)
    Year/source: 1965 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-28/492, July 13-14, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 363-364)
    Year/source: 1972 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-29/493 [MISSING], July 20-21, 1991
  - Show #91-30/494 [MISSING], July 27-28, 1991
  - Show #91-31/495 [MISSING], August 3-4, 1991
  - Show #91-32/496, August 10-11, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 364)
    Year/source: 1964 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-33/497, August 17-18, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 364-365)
    Year/source: 1969 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-34/498, August 24-25, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 365)
    Year/source: 1958 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-35/499, Aug 31-Sept 1, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 365)
  - Show #91-35/500, Sept 7-8, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 365-366)
    Year/source: 1959 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-36/501, Sept 14-15, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 366)
    Year/source: 1971 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-37/502, Sept 21-22, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 366)
    Year/source: 1963 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-38/503, Sept 28-29, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 367)
    Year/source: 1967 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-39/504, Oct -5-6, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 367)
    Year/source: 1960 (T/CD)
  - Show #91-40/505, Oct 12-13, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 367-368)
  - Show #91-41/506, Oct 19-20, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 368)
  - Show #91-42/507, Oct 26-27, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 368)
  - Show #91-43/508, Nov 2-3, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 368-369)
  - Show #91-44/509, Nov 9-10, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 369)
  - Show #91-45/510, Nov 16-17, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 369-370)
  - Show #91-46/511, Nov 23-24, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 370)
  - Show #91-47/512, Nov 30-Dec 1, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 370)
  - Show #91-48/513, Dec 7-8, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 370-371)
  - Show #91-49/514, Dec 14-15, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 371)
  - Show #91-50/515, Dec 21-22, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 371)
    Year/source: 1991 (T)
  - Show #91-51/516, Dec 28-29, 1991; 5 tapes (Oversize 372)
  - Show #92-1/517, Jan 4-5, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 372)
  - Show #92-2/518, Jan 11-12, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 372-373)
  - Show #92-3/519, Jan 18-19, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 373)
  - Show #92-4/520, Jan 25-26, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 373)
  - Show #92-5/521, Feb 1-2, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 373-374)
  - Show #92-6/522, Feb 8-9, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 374)
  - Show #92-7/523, Feb 15-16, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 374-375)
    Year/source: 1970 (T/CD)
  - Show #92-8/524, Feb 22-23, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 375)
    Year/source: 1962 (T/CD)
  - Show #92-9/525, Feb 29-Mar 1, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 375)
    Year/source: 1966 (T/CD)
  - Show #92-10/526, March 7-8, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 375-376)
  - Show #92-11/527, March 14-15, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 376)
  - Show #92-12/528, March 21-22, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 376)
  - Show #92-13/529, March 28-29, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 377)
  - Show #92-14/530, April 4-5, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 377)
  - Show #92-15/531, April 11-12, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 377-378)
    Year/source: 1968 (T/CD)
  - Show #92-16/532, April 18-19, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 378)
  - Show #92-17/533, April 25-26, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 378)
  - Show #92-18/534, May 2-3, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 378-379)
  - Show #92-19/535, May 9-10, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 379)
  - Show #92-20/536, May 16-17, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 379-380)
  - Show #92-21/537, May 23-24, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 380)
  - Show #92-22/538, May 30-31, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 380)
  - Show #92-23/539, June 6-7, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 380-381)
  - Show #92-24/540, June 13-14, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 381)
  - Show #92-25/541, June 20-21, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 381)
  - Show #92-26/542, June 27-28, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 382)
  - Show #92-27/543, July 4-5, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 382)
  - Show #92-28/544, July 11-12, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 382-383)
  - Show #92-29/545, July 18-19, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 383)
  - Show #92-30/546, July 25-26, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 383)
  - Show #92-31/547, August 1-2, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 383-384)
  - Show #92-32/548, August 8-9, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 384)
  - Show #92-33/549, August 15-16, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 384-385)
  - Show #92-34/550, August 22-23, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 385)
  - Show #92-34/550, August 22-23, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 385)
  - Show #92-35/551, August 29-30, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 385)
  - Show #92-35/552, Sept 5-6, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 385-386)
  - Show #92-36/553, Sept 12-13, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 386)
  - Show #92-37/554, Sept 19-20, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 386)
    Artist: Ben E. King
  - Show #92-38/555, Sept 26-27, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 387)
  - Show #92-39/556, Oct -3-4, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 387)
  - Show #92-40/557, Oct 10-11, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 387-388)
  - Show #92-41/558, Oct 17-18, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 388)
  - Show #92-42/559, Oct 24-25, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 388)
  - Show #92-43/560, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 388-389)
  - Show #92-44/561, Nov 7-8, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 389)
  - Show #92-45/562, Nov 14-15, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 390)
  - Show #92-46/563, Nov 21-22, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 390)
  - Show #92-47/564, Nov 28-29, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 390)
  - Show #92-48/565, Dec 5-6, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 390-391)
  - Show #92-49/566, Dec 12-13, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 391)
  - Show #92-50/567, Dec 19-20, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 391)
    Year/source: 1992 (T/CD)
  - Show #92-51/568, Dec 26-27, 1992; 5 tapes (Oversize 392)
  - Show #93-1/569, Jan 2-3, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 392)
  - Show #93-2/570, Jan 9-10, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 392-393)
  - Show #93-3/571, Jan 16-17, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 393)
  - Show #93-4/572, Jan 23-24, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 393)
  - Show #93-5/573, Jan 30-31, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 393-394)
  - Show #93-6/574, Feb 6-7, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 394)
  - Show #93-7/575, Feb 13-14, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 394-395)
    Artist: Love Song Special
  - Show #93-8/576, Feb 20-21, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 395)
  - Show #93-9/577, Feb 27-28, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 395)
  - Show #93-10/578, March 6-7, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 395-396)
    Year/source: 1966 (CD)
  - Show #93-11/579, March 13-14, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 396)
    Year/source: 1969 (CD)
  - Show #93-12/580, March 20-21, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 396)
  - Show #93-13/581, March 27-28, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 397)
  - Show #93-14/582, April 3-4, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 397)
  - Show #93-15/583, April 10-11, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 397-398)
  - Show #93-16/584, April 17-18, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 398)
  - Show #93-17/585, April 24-25, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 398)
    Artist: Salute to Girl Groups
  - Show #93-18/586, May 1-2, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 398-399)
  - Show #93-19/587, May 8-9, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 399)
  - Show #93-20/588, May 15-16, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 399-400)
  - Show #93-21/589, May 22-23, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 400)
  - Show #93-22/590, May 29-30, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 400)
  - Show #93-23/591, June 5-6, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 400-401)
  - Show #93-24/592, June 12-13, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 401)
  - Show #93-25/593, June 19-20, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 401)
  - Show #93-26/594, June 26-27, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 402)
  - Show #93-27/595, July 3-4, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 402)
    Artist: All American Hits
  - Show #93-28/596, July 10-11, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 402-403)
  - Show #93-29/597, July 17-18, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 403)
  - Show #93-30/598, July 24-25, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 403)
    Year/source: 1968 (CD)
  - Show #93-31/599, July 31-Aug 1, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 403-404)
    Year/source: 1964 (CD)
  - Show #93-32/600, August 7-8, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 404)
  - Show #93-33/601, August 14-15, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 404-405)
  - Show #93-34/602, August 21-22, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 405)
  - Show #93-34/602, August 21-22, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 405)
  - Show #93-35/603, August 28-29, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 405)
  - Show #93-35/604, Sept 4-5, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 405-406)
    Artist: Motown Music
  - Show #93-36/605, Sept 11-12, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 406)
  - Show #93-37/606, Sept 18-19, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 406)
  - Show #93-38/607, Sept 25-26, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 407)
  - Show #93-39/608, Oct -2-3, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 407)
  - Show #93-40/609, Oct 9-10, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 407-408)
  - Show #93-41/610, Oct 16-17, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 408)
    Artist: Salute to Phil Spector
  - Show #93-42/611, Oct 23-24, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 408)
  - Show #93-43/612, Oct 30-31, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 408-409)
  - Show #93-44/613, Nov 6-7, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 409)
  - Show #93-45/614, Nov 13-14, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 409-410)
  - Show #93-46/615, Nov 20-21, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 410)
  - Show #93-47/616, Nov 27-28, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 410)
    Year/source: 1967 (CD)
  - Show #93-48/617, Dec 4-5, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 410-411)
    Year/source: 1970 (CD)
    Artist: Frankie Valli
  - Show #93-49/618, Dec 11-12, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 411)
  - Show #93-50/619, Dec 18-19, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 411)
    Year/source: 1993 (T/CD)
  - Show #93-51/620, Dec 25-26, 1993; 5 tapes (Oversize 412)
  - Show #94-1/621, Jan 1-2, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 412)
  - Show #94-2/622, Jan 8-9, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 412-413)
  - Show #94-3/623, Jan 15-16, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 413)
  - Show #94-4/624, Jan 22-23, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 413)
  - Show #94-5/625, Jan 29-30, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 413-414)
  - Show #94-6/626, Feb 5-6, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 414)
  - Show #94-7/627, Feb 12-13, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 414-415)
  - Show #94-8/628, Feb 19-20, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 415)
  - Show #94-9/629, Feb 26-27, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 415)
  - Show #94-10/630, March 5-6, 1994; 5 tapes (Oversize 415-TBD)
  - Additional shows in process
- Recordings, Specials and miscellaneous
  In process, approximately 100 shows.
- Scrapbooks
  In process.
- Scripts
  - American Country Music Awards (ACMA)
    - ACMA Special, 1989 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1990 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1991 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1992 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1993 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1994 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1995 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1996 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1997 (Box 6)
    - ACMA Special, 1998 (Box 7)
    - ACMA Special, 1999 (Box 7)
    - ACMA Special, 2000 (Box 7)
    - ACMA Special, 2001 (Box 7)
  - American Bandstand
    - 33 1/3 Celebration, undated (Box 7)
    - 40th Anniversary, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Back to Bandstand, 18-20 May 1990 (Box 7)
    - Back to Bandstand, 27-28 Apr 1991 (Box 7)
    - Bandstand USA, undated (Box 7)
    - Best of Bandstand, 24-25 Jun 1989 (Box 7)
    - Beach Boys Special, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Continental Airlines, undated; 3 shows for airing in-flight (Box 7)
    - Four Tops/Temptations, undated (Box 7)
    - Memories of Elvis, undated (Box 7)
    - Summer Beach Party, 28-29 May 1994 (Box 8)
  - American Music Awards (AMA)
    - AMA Special, 1988 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1989 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1990 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1991 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1992 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1993 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1994 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1995 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1996 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1997 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 1998 (Box 8)
    - AMA Moments, 1998 (Box 8)
    - AMA Special, 2000 (Box 8)
    - AMA Moments, undated (Box 8)
  - Caravan of Stars, undated (Box 9)
  - Countdown America
    - Countdown to 2000, Aug-Dec 1999; 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Show #166, Dec 31, 1988-Jan 1, 1989; Best of 1988 (Box 9)
    - Show #301-333, cue sheets only; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Show #334, Mar 21-22, 1992; Peter Cetera (Box 9)
    - Show #335, Mar 28-29, 1992; Michael Jackson (Box 9)
    - Show #336, Apr 4-5, 1992; Sting (Box 9)
    - Show #337, Apr 11-12, 1992; Aaron Neville (Box 9)
    - Show #338, Apr 18-19, 1992; Cher (Box 10)
    - Show #339, Apr 25-26, 1992; Rod Stewart (Box 10)
    - Show #340, May 2-3, 1992; Bruce Springsteen (Box 10)
    - Show #341, May 9-10, 1992; Luther Vandross (Box 10)
    - Show #342, May 16-17, 1992; Mariah Carey (Box 10)
    - Show #343, May 23-24, 1992; Paula Abdul (Box 10)
    - Show #344, May 30-31, 1992; Amy Grant (Box 10)
    - Show #345, Jun 6-7, 1992; Carly Simon (Box 10)
    - Show #346, Jun 13-14, 1992; Genesis (Box 10)
    - Show #347, Jun 20-21, 1992; Lionel Richie (Box 10)
    - Show #348, Jun 27-28, 1992; Steve Winwood (Box 10)
    - Show #349, Jul 4-5, 1992; Rick Astley (Box 10)
    - Show #350, Jul 11-12, 1992; Madonna (Box 10)
    - Show #351, Jul 18-19, 1992; Loggins & Messina (Box 10)
    - Show #352, Jul 25-26, 1992; Gloria Estefan/MSM (Box 10)
    - Show #353, Aug 1-2, 1992; James Taylor (Box 10)
    - Show #354, Aug 8-9, 1992; Natalie Cole (Box 10)
    - Show #355, Aug 15-16, 1992; Richard Marx (Box 11)
    - Show #356, Aug 22-23, 1992; Elton John (Box 11)
    - Show #357, Aug 29-30, 1992; Smokey Robinson (Box 11)
    - Show #358, Sep 5-6, 1992; Paul Simon (Box 11)
    - Show #359, Sep 12-13, 1992; Billy Joel (Box 11)
    - Show #360, Sep 19-20, 1992; Peter Cetera (Box 11)
    - Show #361, Sep 26-27, 1992; Beach Boys (Box 11)
    - Show #362, Oct 3-4, 1992; John Lennon (Box 11)
    - Show #363, Oct 10-11, 1992; Neil Diamond (Box 11)
    - Show #364, Oct 17-18, 1992; Fleetwood Mac (Box 11)
    - Show #365, Oct 24-25, 1992; Cher (Box 11)
    - Show #366, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1992; Michael Jackson (Box 11)
    - Show #367, Nov 7-8, 1992; Bob Seger (Box 11)
    - Show #368, Nov 14-15, 1992; Hall & Oates (Box 11)
    - Show #369, Nov 21-22, 1992; Janet Jackson (Box 11)
    - Show #370, Nov 28-29, 1992; George Michael (Box 11)
    - Show #371, Dec 5-6, 1992; Genesis (Box 11)
    - Show #372, Dec 12-13, 1992; Whitney Houston (Box 11)
    - Show #373, Dec 19-20, 1992; Michael Bolton (Box 12)
    - Show #374, Dec 26-27, 1992; Best of 1992, Part 1 (Box 12)
    - Show #375, 1993 Jan 2-3; cue sheets only (Box 12)
  - Dick Clark's Days to Remember, 2000; 12 folders (Box 12)
  - Dick Clark's Music Calendar, 2002, Apr-May (Box 13)
  - Dick Clark's Music Calendar, 2004, Sep-Dec (Box 13)
  - Rock, Roll and Remember
    - Show #002-008, cue sheets only (Box 13)
    - Show #009, Apr 10-11, 1982; Neil Sedaka (Box 13)
    - Show #010, Apr 17-18, 1982; Johnny Mathis (Box 13)
    - Show #011, Apr 24-25, 1982; Everly Brothers (Box 13)
    - Show #012, May 1-2, 1982; Frankie & Annette (Box 13)
    - Show #013, May 8-9, 1982; Hall & Oates (Box 13)
    - Show #014, May 15-16, 1982; Dion (Box 13)
    - Show #015, May 22-23, 1982; Righteous Brothers (Box 13)
    - Show #016, May 29-30, 1982; Elton John (Box 13)
    - Show #017, Jun 5-6, 1982; Johnny Rivers (Box 13)
    - Show #018, Jun 12-13, 1982; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 13)
    - Show #019, Jun 19-20, 1982; Bread (Box 13)
    - Show #020, Jun 26-27, 1982; Bobby Vinton (Box 14)
    - Show #021, Jul 3-4, 1982; Beach Boys (Box 14)
    - Show #022, Jul 10-11, 1982; Association (Box 14)
    - Show #023, Jul 17-18, 1982; Jan & Dean (Box 14)
    - Show #024, Jul 24-25, 1982; Carpenters (Box 14)
    - Show #025, Jul 31-Aug 1, 1982; Captain & Tennille (Box 14)
    - Show #026, Aug 7-8, 1982; Peter Noone (Box 14)
    - Show #027, Aug 14-15, 1982; Curtis Mayfield (Box 14)
    - Show #028, Aug 21-22, 1982; Billy Joel (Box 14)
    - Show #029, Aug 28-29, 1982; Chubby Checker (Box 14)
    - Show #030, Sep 4-5, 1982; Elvis Presley Special (Box 14)
    - Show #031, Sep 11-12, 1982; Monkees (Box 14)
    - Show #032, Sep 18-19, 1982; Olivia Newton-John2 copies (Box 14)
    - Show #033, Sep 25-26, 1982; Chicago (Box 15)
    - Show #034, Oct 2-3, 1982; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 15)
    - Show #035, Oct 9-10, 1982; Rascals (Box 15)
    - Show #036, Oct 16-17, 1982; Connie Francis (Box 15)
    - Show #037, Oct 23-24, 1982; Peter, Paul & Mary (Box 15)
    - Show #038, Oct 30-31, 1982; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 15)
    - Show #039, Nov 7-8, 1982; Hollies (Box 15)
    - Show #040, Nov 14-15, 1982; Byrds (Box 15)
    - Show #041, Nov 21-22, 1982; B.J. Thomas (Box 15)
    - Show #042, Nov 28-29, 1982; Bobby Vee (Box 15)
    - Show #043, Dec 4-5, 1982; Spinners (Box 15)
    - Show #044, Dec 11-12, 1982; Brenda Lee (Box 15)
    - Show #044, Dec 11-12, 1982; Brenda Lee [copy 2] (Box 16)
    - Show #045, Dec 18-19, 1982; Coasters (Box 16)
    - Show #046, Dec 25-26, 1982; RRR Christmas Show (Box 16)
    - Show #047, Jan 1-2, 1983; Year End Review (1982) (Box 16)
    - Show #048, Jan 8-9, 1983; Guess Who (Box 16)
    - Show #049, Jan 15-16, 1983; Tommy Roe (Box 16)
    - Show #050, Jan 22-23, 1983; Kinks (Box 16)
    - Show #051, Jan 29-30, 1983; Jimmy Rodgers (Box 16)
    - Show #052, Feb 5-6, 1983; Shirelles (Box 16)
    - Show #053, Feb 12-13, 1983; Grass Roots (Box 17)
    - Show #054, Feb 19-20, 1983; Electric Light Orchestra (Box 17)
    - Show #055, Feb 26-27, 1983; Peter & Gordon (Box 17)
    - Show #056, Mar 5-6, 1983; Turtles (Box 17)
    - Show #057, Mar 12-13, 1983; Little River Band (Box 17)
    - Show #058, Mar 19-20, 1983; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 17)
    - Show #059, Mar 26-27, 1983; Miracles (Box 17)
    - Show #060, Apr 2-3, 1983; Helen Reddy (Box 18)
    - Show #061, Apr 9-10, 1983; America (Box 18)
    - Show #062, Apr 16-17, 1983; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 18)
    - Show #063, Apr 23-24, 1983; Leslie Gore (Box 18)
    - Show #064, Apr30-May 1, 1983; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 18)
    - Show #065, May 7-8, 1983; Air Supply (Box 18)
    - Show #066, May 14-15, 1983; Pat Boone (Box 18)
    - Show #067, May 21-22, 1983; Ray Charles (Box 19)
    - Show #068, May 28-29, 1983; Animals (Box 19)
    - Show #069, Jun 4-5, 1983; Bob Seger (Box 19)
    - Show #070, Jun 11-12, 1983; Roy Orbison (Box 19)
    - Show #071, Jun 18-19, 1983; Paul Anka (Box 19)
    - Show #072, Jun 25-26, 1983; Dionne Warwick (Box 19)
    - Show #073, Jul 2-3, 1983; Drifters (Box 19)
    - Show #074, Jul 9-10, 1983; Crosby, Stills & Nash (Box 20)
    - Show #075, Jul 16-17, 1983; Bobby Rydell (Box 20)
    - Show #076, Jul 23-24, 1983; Loggins & Messina (Box 20)
    - Show #077, Jul 30-31, 1983; Everly Brothers (Box 20)
    - Show #078, Aug 6-7, 1983; ABBA (Box 20)
    - Show #079, Aug 13-14, 1983; Three Dog Night (Box 20)
    - Show #080, Aug 20-21, 1983; Ray Stevens (Box 20)
    - Show #081, Aug 27-28, 1983; Petula Clark (Box 21)
    - Show #082, Sep 3-4, 1983; Bee Gees (Box 21)
    - Show #083, Sep 10-11, 1983; Al Green (Box 21)
    - Show #084, Sep 17-18, 1983; Dion (Box 21)
    - Show #085, Sep 25-26, 1983; The Platters (Box 21)
    - Show #086, Oct 1-2, 1983; Tom Jones (Box 21)
    - Show #087, Oct 8-9, 1983; Dr. Hook (Box 21)
    - Show #088, Oct 15-16, 1983; Jerry Butler (Box 22)
    - Show #089, Oct 22-23, 1983; Jackson Five (Box 22)
    - Show #090, Oct 29-30, 1983; Hall & Oates (Box 22)
    - Show #091, Nov 5-6, 1983; Fifth Dimension (Box 22)
    - Show #092, Nov 12-13, 1983; Charlie Rich (Box 22)
    - Show #093, Nov 19-20, 1983; Mamas and the Papas (Box 22)
    - Show #094, Nov 26-27, 1983; Stevie Wonder (Box 22)
    - Show #095, Dec 3-4, 1983; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 23)
    - Show #096, Dec 10-11, 1983; Neil Sedaka (Box 23)
    - Show #097, Dec 17-18, 1983; Jr. Walker & the Allstars (Box 23)
    - Show #098, Dec 24-25, 1983; RRR Christmas Show (Box 23)
    - Show #099, Dec 31, 1983-Jan 1, 1984; Year End Review (1983) (Box 23)
    - Show #100, Jan 7-8, 1984; Brook Benton (Box 23)
    - Show #101, Jan 14-15, 1984; Little Richard (Box 23)
    - Show #102, Jan 21-22, 1984; Elton John (Box 24)
    - Show #103, Jan 28-29, 1984; Anne Murray (Box 24)
    - Show #104, Feb 4-5, 1984; Marvin Gaye (Box 24)
    - Show #105, Feb 11-12, 1984; Carly Simon (Box 24)
    - Show #106, Feb 18-19, 1984; Association (Box 24)
    - Show #107, Feb 25-26, 1984; Mary Wells (Box 24)
    - Show #108, Mar 3-4, 1984; Jackie Wilson (Box 24)
    - Show #109, Mar 10-11, 1984; Searchers (Box 25)
    - Show #110, Mar 17-18, 1984; Seals & Crofts (Box 25)
    - Show #111, Mar 24-25, 1984; Temptations (Box 25)
    - Show #112, Mar 31- Apr 1, 1984; Bread (Box 25)
    - Show #113, Apr 7-8, 1984; Monkees (Box 25)
    - Show #114, Apr 14-15, 1984; Roberta Flack (Box 25)
    - Show #115, Apr 21-22, 1984; Peter, Paul & Mary (Box 25)
    - Show #116, Apr 28-29, 1984; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 26)
    - Show #117, May 5-6, 1984; Supremes (Box 26)
    - Show #118, May 12-13, 1984; Duane Eddy (Box 26)
    - Show #119, May 19-20, 1984; Stylistics (Box 26)
    - Show #120, May 26-27, 1984; Fleetwood Mac (Box 26)
    - Show #121, Jun 2-3, 1984; B J Thomas (Box 26)
    - Show #122, Jun 9-10, 1984; Righteous Brothers (Box 26)
    - Show #123, Jun 16-17, 1984; Pat Boone (Box 27)
    - Show #124, Jun 23-24, 1984; Ray Charles (Box 27)
    - Show #125, Jun 30-Jul 1, 1984; Four Tops (Box 27)
    - Show #126, Jul 7-8, 1984; Captain & Tennille (Box 27)
    - Show #127, Jul 14-15, 1984; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 27)
    - Show #128, Jul 21-22, 1984; Tom Jones (Box 27)
    - Show #129, Jul 28-29, 1984; Three Dog Night (Box 27)
    - Show #130, Aug 4-5, 1984; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 27)
    - Show #131, Aug 11-12, 1984; Spinners (Box 28)
    - Show #132, Aug 18-19, 1984; Herman’s Hermits (Box 28)
    - Show #133, Aug 25-26, 1984; Animals (Box 28)
    - Show #134, Sep 1-2, 1984; Bee Gees (Box 28)
    - Show #135, Sep 8-9, 1984; O’Jays (Box 28)
    - Show #136, Sep 15-16, 1984; America (Box 28)
    - Show #137, Sep 22-23, 1984; Shirelles (Box 28)
    - Show #138, Sep 29-30, 1984; Dionne Warwick (Box 29)
    - Show #139, Oct 7-8, 1984; Jay & the Americans (Box 29)
    - Show #140, Oct 14-15, 1984; Sly & the Family Stone (Box 29)
    - Show #141, Oct 21-22, 1984; Neil Diamond (Box 29)
    - Show #142, Oct 28-29, 1984; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 29)
    - Show #143, Nov 3-4, 1984; Everly Brothers (Box 29)
    - Show #144, Nov 10-11, 1984; Chubby Checker (Box 29)
    - Show #145, Nov 17-18, 1984; Commodores (Box 30)
    - Show #146, Nov 24-25, 1984; Jan & Dean (Box 30)
    - Show #147, Dec 1-2, 1984; Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass (Box 30)
    - Show #148, Dec 8-9, 1984; Donny Osmond (Box 30)
    - Show #149, Dec 15-16, 1984; Earth Wind & Fire (Box 30)
    - Show #150, Dec 22-23, 1984; RRR Christmas Show (Box 30)
    - Show #151, Dec 29-30, 1984; Chicago (Box 30)
    - Show #152, Jan 5-6, 1985; Elvis Presley (Box 30)
    - Show #152, Jan 5-6, 1985; Elvis Presleycopy 2 (Box 31)
    - Show #153, Jan 12-13, 1985; Electric Light Orchestra (Box 31)
    - Show #154, Jan 19-20, 1985; Donovan (Box 31)
    - Show #155, Jan 26-27, 1985; Little Richard (Box 31)
    - Show #156, Feb 2-3, 1985; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 31)
    - Show #157, Feb 9-10, 1985; Bobby Vee (Box 31)
    - Show #158, Feb 16-17, 1985; Byrds (Box 31)
    - Show #159, Feb 23-24, 1985; Four Seasons (Box 31)
    - Show #160, Mar 2-3, 1985; Johhny Rivers (Box 32)
    - Show #161, Mar 9-10, 1985; Bobby Vinton (Box 32)
    - Show #162, Mar 16-17, 1985; Grass Roots (Box 32)
    - Show #163, Mar 23-24, 1985; Brook Benton (Box 32)